<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>
    
    <string name="VIInews">Argentine actress and former model Silvina Luna passed away on August 31 after battling health complications stemming from a 2011 plastic surgery carried out by cosmetic surgeon Anibal Lotocki. The actress had undergone a butt lift surgery in the year 2011. The 43-year-old, who had been suffering from kidney failure for more than a decade, had spent 79 days in hospital before his brother reportedly permitted the medical team to remove her from the life support. Doctors first came to know of her condition in 2015 when she was being treated for kidney stone. She was diagnosed with renal insufficiency and was put on weekly dialysis. Later in 2016, doctor Cristian Perez performed a surgery on her and removed the toxic substance from her body. He had then told the media that Silvina had developed an autoimmune disease caused by the medications as a consequence of her surgeries. All patients develop severe kidney failure and end up dying. This isnt an isolated case of a cosmetic surgery gone wrong, many celebrities have suffered complications after plastic surgery . Kim Kardashian lookalike, Christina Ashten Gourkani, passed away due to cardiac arrest in April 2023 following a cosmetic surgery procedure. In may, 21-year-old Kannada TV actor Chethana Raj died reportedly while undergoing a fat removal procedure. Punjabi actor Vivek Shauq lost his life while undergoing liposuction at a hospital in Thane in the year 2011, while Telugu actor Aarthi Agarwal died due to cardiac arrest at a US hospital in 2015. She was also undergoing a fat removal process. For more news and updates, stay tuned to ETimes.</string>
    <string name="VInews">In June 2021, one of Elon Musks children, Xavier Alexander Musk, filed a request to change her name in accordance with her new gender identity. She expressed a desire to disassociate from her biological father in every possible way. Now, a new assertion by Musks biographer, Walter Isaacson, in an excerpt from his book titled published in The Wall Street Journal, suggests that Musks daughter informed her aunt about her gender transition but asked her not to her father about it. Since then, Musk adopted a strong anti-"woke" stance as a result of his childs gender transition. According to a book, Musk has called his daughter a "Communist" and believes she broke off her relationship with him because she was influenced by her school in California,</string>
    <string name="Vnews">The education department in Shivamogga district of Karnataka, transferred a government school teacher and initiated an inquiry against her after she allegedly asked two Class 5 Muslim students to “go to Pakistan”, officials familiar with the matter said on Saturday. We were shocked after the children told us about the incident. We filed a complaint with Deputy Director of Public Instruction (DDPI), and the department took action against the teacher,” he added.
Block Education Officer B. Nagaraj, who conducted a probe into the incident, said the other students of class corroborated with the complaint.</string>
    <string name="IVnews">Odisha Chief Minister Naveen Patnaik on Saturday felicitated javelin star Kishore Jena with a cash award of Rs. 50 lakhs for his outstanding performance in Javelin throw and reaching the finals of the prestigious World Athletics Championship that recently concluded in Budapest, Hungary. This is the first time that an Odisha athlete has reached this feat.
In a historic first for the World Athletics Championships, three Indian athletes secured their positions in the men’s Javelin final that included Kishore from Odisha. He further strengthened his position in the javelin world when he finished 5th with a personal best of 84.77 m and made his state very proud while also making an impression on the Athletics fraternity of the world.</string>
    <string name="IIInews">President Droupadi Murmu on Saturday summoned both Rajya Sabha and Lok Sabha to meet on September 18, the day when the five-sitting long Special Session of Parliament will begin. In a notification to both Houses separately, President Murmu said, "In exercise of the powers conferred upon me by clause (1) of article 85 of the Constitution, I hereby summon the Lok Sabha, Rajya Sabha, to meet at New Delhi on Monday, the 18th September 2023 at 11.00 A.M." Union Parliamentary Affairs Minister Pralhad Joshi on Thursday informed about the five-day special session of Parliament from September 18 to 22. The agenda for this special session, however, was not revealed.</string>
    <string name="IInews">Shiv Sena (UBT) MP Sanjay Raut on Sunday hit out at the BJP-led union government for calling a special session of Parliament during Ganesh Utsav, saying people of Maharashtra observe fast and dont leave home during the festival. While the agenda of the five-day Parliament session has been kept under wraps, Raut claimed that the prime minister wants to have discussions on “China invading Ladakh” and the Manipur issue. “In Maharashtra, we have Ganesh Utsav so we cant go. Modi ji would never call a special session of Parliament during Navratri,” the Shiv Sena leader told reporters.
“We have heard that PM Modi wants to have a discussion on China invading Ladakh and the Manipur issue. China has published a new map showing Ladakh as its territory.”</string>
    <string name="Inews">Senior advocate Harish Salve on Thursday told the Supreme Court that Article 370 was a “political compromise” arrived at the time of accession and integration of Jammu and Kashmir into India, given the situation and the fact that there were more than one view on the subject. It was a political compromise…. There were sharp differences even in the Congress Working Committee. They rejected this plan. Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel’s letter says, ‘sorry, I don’t accept this’…. There was the spectre of the United Nations….This was a matter with…competing points of view. So this was the compromise which was incorporated in the Constitution,” Salve told a five-judge Constitution bench presided by CJI D Y Chandrachud, which is hearing petitions challenging changes made to Article 370.
He told the bench that this was the “workable arrangement. They said alright, ultimately we will decide and we will keep to ourselves the power to dis-apply this Article. But if this works, phase by phase…why not? And it did work to a large extent.”</string>
</resources>